bloggingunderground.com 2017-12-14

# Blogging Underground Privacy Policy | Blogging Underground

**Blogging Underground Privacy Policy**

We respect your privacy and make every effort to protect your personal information and will not share your email address with anyone else period. We will only occasionally send you email messages with important news and info and will not send you junk.

Blogging Underground (“Blogging Underground” or “the Site” or “our” or “Creative Power”) has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our web visitors and members.

In adopting this privacy policy, the intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using personally identifiable information and a user’s reasonable expectations of privacy.

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Blogging Underground Site:

**Information collected from All Users**

Basic Non-Identifiable web usage statistics as collected in statistical applications and access logs.

**Cookies – session id’s**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes.  Blogging Underground may use both “session ID cookies” and “persistent cookies.” Blogging Underground uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, provide convenience features and for other purposes.

Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

  Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.

**Information collected from Registered Users**

Registered users voluntariliy provide personal and/or payment information which is only used internally for the purpose of delivering features and services as requested by users. We do not share this information with any other parties and in many cases do not store the data internally. We do not store any personal or payment data where it is publicly accessible, however we may employ the use of thrid-party applications to provide information and services.

Payment information is used for purposes of billing and order fulfillment. This includes, but is not limited to, sending a user’s billing information to a credit card processor or providing a user’s postal address to a shipping company.

**Public Disclosure**

The Blogging Underground Site may include features, such as discussion forums, blog posts, linking tools, blog posting tools, comment forms and related tools, that allow users to publicly share information about themselves. Any information a user discloses in these areas is publicly available on the Internet. Such information may be read, archived, collected, or used by other Internet users, including automated services such as search engines. Blogging Underground is not responsible for personally identifiable information you choose to publicly disclose, and urges users to exercise caution when disclosing information that may be personal in nature. We are also not responsibile for managing any information you may post on sites we don’t own or control, such as announcement blogs provided by 3rd Parties.

**Third Party Websites**

We do not manage and are not responsible for external “third party websites” you may have found through links or articles on Blogging Underground. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by the Blogging Underground Site. Information you share or content you post on contributed blogs and/or third party websites are not within our control and we do not manage or offer to edit, modify or remove any information you have voluntarily provided to the third party websites. It is your responsibility to contact thrid party websites directly if you have issues with data or information or content you have provided them.

**Security Methods**

Blogging Underground employs reasonable security methods to secure users’ privacy, including, but not limited to, third-party encryption of payment forms, password protected file systems and similar means of protection, designed to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. While Blogging Underground takes commercially reasonable security precautions, the Site is not responsible for data breaches of third parties, such as payment processors, web hosts or advertising providers.

**Unsubscribe and Cancellation Options**

Blogging Underground users may request that their personal information be deleted from Site records by sending an email to 

Blogging Underground will remove personally identifiable information from its records for any user that requests removal, provided that the user’s account remains inactive for seven days. Any user whose information is removed from Site records shall thereafter be bound by rules for “All Users,” as provided above, except that information in the public domain, such as a user’s forum or blog posts while a Registered User, will not be deleted from the Site’s and/or records.

**Disclosure by Legal Mandate**

Blogging Underground reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by legal mandate, including, but not limited to, compliance with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process lawfully served on Blogging Underground.

**Children Under Thirteen Years of Age**

Pursuant to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), Blogging Underground generally does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under thirteen (13) years of age. Blogging Underground only collects information from children under thirteen years of age after receiving verified parental consent prior to collection. Upon notice that Blogging Underground has inadvertently collected personally identifiable information from a child under thirteen, Blogging Underground will take all reasonable steps to remove such information from its records as quickly as reasonably possible.

**Transition of Ownership**

Were Blogging Underground to engage in a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition or sale, your personally identifiable information may be among the assets transferred. Users will be notified of any ownership transition via prominent notice on the Site at least thirty (30) days before any such change in ownership or control of your personal information is undertaken.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Blogging Underground reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on the Blogging Underground Site. This Blogging Underground Privacy Policy was last updated on June 9, 2010.

**Contact Information**

Mike Liebner

Blogging Underground

Creative Power

12400 Ventura Blvd. #207

Studio City, CA 91604

(310) 734-1574
